<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tea Cuppy</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tea</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Timer</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Personal</string>
    <string name="tab_text_4">Places</string>
    <string name="select">Select</string>

    <string name="tea_details">Tea Details</string>
    <string name="tea_add">Add Tea</string>


    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>


    <string name="black_tea_description">

    Black tea is one of the most commonm tea around the world. It is produced when dried tea leaves are
        rolled and allowed to oxidize, developing a natural flavor and color in the leaf.

    </string>
    <string name="green_tea_description">

        Green tea is a type of tea originated from China.  It is made from Camellia sinensis leaves and buds that
        have not undergone the same oxidation process as those of black teas and oolong teaas.


    </string>

    <string name="oolong_tea_description">

        Oolong is a semi-oxidized tea that originated from China. It is produced through the process of its leaves
        withering under the sun and oxidationg into a curly and twisty shape.


    </string>

    <string name="puerh_tea_description">

        Pu-erh tea is made from the leaves and stems of the Camellia sinensis plant. This is the same
        plant as that of oolong and black tea leaves, but having undergone a different process.

    </string>
    <string name="white_tea_description">

        White tea is produced from the Camellia sinensis plant, similar to that of black tea, however
        with the key difference of having undergone minimal processing.

    </string>
    <string name="matcha_tea_description">

        Matcha is the finely ground powder that has been specially grown and processed from green tea leaves.
    </string>


    <string name="herbal_tea_description">

        Herbal teas are made through the infusion of herbs, spices, or other plant material in hot water.

    </string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tea_detail">TeaDetail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tea_add">TeaAdd</string>
</resources>
